### Jin Chen Lim

### 3373D 300D • JBLM, WA 98433

Mobile: (916) 799-0755 • Email: jiclim@ucdavis.edu

<u>Professional Summary:</u> A dedicated and experienced supervisor who presided over high number assets and personnel implementing various strategies supporting business and financial objectives. Capable of working alone or as a member of a team, and comfortable exercising initiative and solving problems. Trained and supported coworkers. Qualifications include:

- Microsoft Word Certified
- Microsoft Excel Certified
- Maintenance Manager

- · Experienced Leader
- Supply Chain Management
- · Training and Mentoring

#### Education

EMT Registry No. E3180824 (May 2015) BS, Animal Science (June 2013) University of California, Davis Medical Logistics Specialist

### **Work Experience**

US Army JBLM,, WA

JUN 2016-PRESENT

### Combat Health Sergeant/Training Room NCO

- Developed MASCAL protocols and evacuated 30 Soldiers quickly and efficiently with a three man team
- Provided emergency medical care and continual care during evacuation
- Managed BOSS program for Joint Base Lewis-McChord overseeing three coworkers affecting over 10,000 people.
- Improved medical supply ordering, organization and distribution that affected over 300 Soldiers
- Trained and mentored 5 co-workers on medical supply chain and medical knowledge
- Managed over 150+ personal, providing admins support and assistance

# **Better Opportunities for Single Soldiers (BOSS)** JBLM, WA

**BOSS President** 

SEP 2017- PRESENT

- Volunteer over 400+ Hours at VA homes and other nonprofit organizations
- Increased fundraising efforts and raised over \$10K
- Increased volunteer hours donated to community with 2k hours logged
- Improved over 40 veteran's quality of life through building renovations and area beautification
- Improved relationship between BOSS and other volunteer organizations garnering additional opportunities
- Represented and briefed at various meetings showcasing a summary of organization activities
- Increased social media presence through FB and Instagram, gaining followers and engaged conversations

# Jackson Rancheria Casino Jackson, CA

**EMT/Security** 

- Provided emergency medical care for employees and guests, assisting in a variety of medical situations.
- Provide guest with non-medical assistance
- Secured the safety of casino assets and personal

### US ARMY RESERVE Sacramento, CA

DEC 2011- JUN 2016

MAR 2015-JUN 2016

Medical Logistics Specialist

- Maintain, record and order medical supplies
- Trained to set up and maintain emergency centers
- Certified in sanitation and lifesaving procedures

### **Volunteer Experience**

## Front Street Animal Shelter Volunteer

2127 Front Street, Sacramento, CA 95818

FEB 2014-APR 2015

- Supervised Teen Program
- Helped train dogs for adoption
- Taught teenage volunteers customer service skills
- Organized documents to be distributed at fundraisers for the shelter.
- Assembled adoption packets for pets.
- Trained animals that are placed for adoption.

References Available Upon Request

Awards:

Spirit of Service 2019 - WA American Legion Chapter

Best BOSS President 2019 - Better Opportunities for Single Service Members